

Garland, TX 75044 • <u>James.Sole20@gmail.com</u> • (469) 602-6277

Career Objectives

Diligent IT Management major currently attending Tarleton State University, with 8.5 years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of web platform development, web design, and application development skills to successfully fill the UI UX role at your company. Frequently praised as a creative hard-working designer by my peers and management, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

Education

Tarleton State UniversityStephenville, TXBachelor of Science in IT ManagementMay 2024

GoCreate USA Bootcamp
UI/UX Designer Certification (Using Figma)
Online
May 2023

Coding Dojo

Dallas, TX

Certification in Full Stack Web Development (in Python, MEAN, Ruby on Rails)

May 2018

Richland Collegiate High School Dallas, TX

Associate of Science in Computer and Information Sciences

May 2017

Experience

Careington International Frisco, TX

Lead Web Designer April 2019-Present

- Design, build and maintain websites with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, content creation tools, management tools, and digital media.
- Confer with management and development teams to prioritize needs, resolve conflicts, develop content criteria, and choose solutions.
- Create web models and prototypes using Adobe XD that include physical, interface, logical, and data models.
- Perform website tests according to planned schedules, and after any website or product revisions.

Soul Form Garland, TX

Lead Creative Director December 2019- Present

- Formulate, direct and coordinate website developments to promote products and services advertised by client.
- Qualify and discover a brand's identity to display a brand's elegant and approachable logo.
- Create a positive prospective customer experience by designing responsive screens.
- Increase user interaction through clever and effective User Interface designs.

1st Choice Adult Day Center

Dallas, TX

Data Specialist May 2018- Present

- Design and validate organizations' databases including designing or testing logic checks.
- Automated client information to streamline paperwork redundancies.
- Managed team of data entry specialists to complete state-required filing.
- Process client data including receipt, entry, verification, and filing of information.

Skills & Interests

• User-centered Product Interaction • User Interface • Information Design Design Design Architecture Strategy Wire-framing User Experience • Adobe XD HTML Photoshop **CSS** JavaScript Illustrator UX Research Figma